Here we are talking about talking but
also researching water fuel process in
uh a place in Australia which we will
remain nameless just for now. And this
is the car and this is the engine of
course. Well, what we've got here today
is what we saw the other day, a water
fuel cell,
as you can see, zooming
in. And I figured a good picture on
that. There's um mesh in there, a core,
three three
um meshes in there, a center electrode,
negative or positive, doesn't matter.
And then a floating unit that's not
connected, it's insulated from
everything else. And then an outer mesh
filled with water, a teaspoon of costic
in about 4 L. So this is about 1/4
teaspoon to 2
L. Um here we'll see the gauge is a
vacuum gauge. The maximum the vacuum
runs in that direction as it increases.
The tube here runs flexibly all the way
in and under the um cabby where
the where the normal um breather off the
manifold comes in. I'll just get a shot
of that
round coming in underneath there. If you
can see that with that back
[Music]
light. Anyway,
so what we're going to do is kick the
engine over. Then we'll do a reading off
the vacuum. Then we're going to read off
this
um volt meter. It comes on about 13
volts and then then decays.
Now this unit will work under as long as
a vacuum is
connected and produce
gas without being electrically
connected. Now we're going to
electrically connect
it and you see a lot more
gas. 13 volts
approximately. So now we'll connect the
voltmeter up.
You come and hold the ball around
please.
Peter fingers up. The fingers are
Peter Peter
fingers. Focus on the voltmeter. 8 75
74 13.7.
Now
disconnecting. It's dropping down to I
said
1.3. That was quick.
Now you got 1.2 vols. There's still
bubbles being formed in the chamber
there in the
cell. 1.14 vol. Still gas coming
out. There's no connection on the
battery there.
down to 1.01
volts.
[Music]
Okay. All right. stabilizing about 170
milliamps. About 10 minutes later after
we charged it and it dropped down to
below 1 volt now the 700 should drop
down
to 70. We'll check it again in a minute
or
two. Okay,
it's the voltmeter is reading 700 m
volts. Now
this stage this unit's charged. It will
apparently um pick up the the vapor very
very quickly uh because we've charged
it. It's now HOH
um hydrogen oxygen and hydrogen easily
separate. I'll just touch it so that you
can see it coming away from the actual
unit. See how that producing there. And
now I just touch the uh the ignition.
That's still connected. I'll now
disconnect. Watch
the produces exactly what you require at
the time.
The worst part about this is that you're
now getting more water out these doors,
which you could in fact recirculate and
make the unit operate fully.
[Music]
Yeah, but it's no good. No, blow
yourself up with that. What do you
actually wire it up to then? Nothing.
[Music]
Cuz it's
char about 5 minutes before
that's producing its own gas. See the
gas? Yeah. And when you hook it up to
original battery, then your water fills
full of
See how that vapor immediately comes
off.
[Music]
That's what my
unit. You will get heaps more vapor when
you have a stainless steel outside.
Yeah. Understand? But just for the
practical purpose of being able to see
it. Yeah.
That's now with it now connected.
Oh, that's not good. See, actually that
that verifies my idea on these
extendable
units because you can see that it's only
using steel the gas what it is pulling
off under its own. You see? And it's not
using any of it. Yeah. See that? That
means that when you have a flexible
unit, the gas you produce with current
[Music]
expans a pressure
gauge means that you you haven't got
your vacuum lift on the water. Right.
Yeah. Right. When you got a solid
container, you can lift that amount of
water clean out through the top because
you take off your vacuum there. You got
pressure because the lid is pressurized.
Does that make sense? Yeah. Good. Cuz
you can just take all
that amount of places straight in under
the
unit where your venturi
lead your motor goes directly under your
throttle under your car.
[Music]
We we're putting the gas directly in
where the exhaust gas uh or the bypass
blow gas that comes from the top of the
motor goes directly under your your
throttle. It's um under the carburetor
so that you've got maximum vacuum
directly into the motor.
Okay. the with um with the vacuum gas
and everything else you you have to have
gas to motor usage air and gas um intake
of air and gas to the um exact fine
critical point. It's a hair whisker
flying. The same as the distributor.
When you cut off your petrol and go to
your gas on petrol, you can turn your
distributor like that and it hardly does
anything to your motor. Mhm. When you
put the gas on, you move it,
not even the width of a piece of foam
and
paper. And your motor will shake like
anything or shape like anything either
way. And you have to hit that exact
point or else you won't get your
efficiency. You won't get your motor to
run. a distributor. The distributor has
to come when you cut off your petrol. If
you run petrol by itself, you are you
set at your normal um whatever it is 8°
or whatever. Um if you um if you hook up
the petrol and gas, you would then
instead of eight, you would come up to
say about 15 12 to 15. When you cut out
petrol all together, you would come from
15 up to somewhere in about 25 to 30,
maybe more. depends on the the vehicle.
Whatever vehicle is all different by
that, but you have to come straight
around to that. You can start it at your
30° advance
um with your gas off your ignition and
she will start like that first go. If
you go back to one drop of petrol with
the gas, she will go like the timing is
too far advanced like normal. Right? So,
if you go back to your petrol, she's too
far advanced. If you're on the gas,
she'll pearl over like she's just
starting on normal petrol. So, it's that
critical of alignment. And when you mix
with your vacuum and everything, you
have to get your right gas to your right
air with the G with hydrogen oxygen back
in. And if you don't get that, it's that
critical that she won't go either.
[Music]
We're all in experimental stage, right?
I'm not going into it, but I have had a
Rover 3500 V8 with twin carbish zenith
same as SU carbage running and that was
where the
soly I didn't understand why the vehicle
seemed to start and run perfectly when
nobody else seems to be able to hit it
was a P76 V8. Now the whole motor on it
is open. It has an open dipstick. It has
an open oil cap. It has a open motor. It
has a a petrol pump on the bottom which
has two little breather holes in it and
they are open which air goes to the sun.
Now I have never had it running on a
solid stainless hydrogen unit because
two things happened. I've had it running
on a polyine unit with plates in it
which you have on tape and that unit
expanded when you powered on it
expanded. There was a pressure there
when I first hooked it up hooked up to
the motor. The motor polluted 10 times
worse than on petrol. 10 times worse and
it had a pressure. It was pressurizing
the sump out, but it was dangerous
hooking up to a polyine unit or an
expandable unit or a contracting one of
any sort, whether it's stainless and it
can expand under under acceleration or
anything. It's dangerous. It'll blow
up. So, the the Rover V8 uh the the
sorry, it run I went from Casino to
Lismo and back again polluting in the
motor itself all the way. But I don't
know why you can blow yourself up
because that unit was expanding under
acceleration. The unit just expanded
out. If that gas can get out anywhere,
you're gone. The car, everything around
gone. With a solid unit, it does the
opposite.
The solid unit has a vacuum to the sump.
Gives you tremendous power. Gives you
tremendous backing off and gives you
smooth running economy and no danger. No
pollution. No pollution in the motor or
out the exhaust at all. None. We've had
readings on that. We put it over a
analyzer and it don't
read. You put a polyine unit on and you
get the opposite effect. You get a
pressure in your sump which then blows
fumes and smoke and soot and out.
But it also pressurizes a unit. It also
makes everything wrong. Wrong way to go.
So they're the two things I've had that
I've made a few units. I've made polyine
ones. I've made um stainless steel ones.
I've made stainless steel ones. What can
extend under? And they're very very very
dangerous. polytheine ones don't seem to
be as dangerous, but no one in the
world's going to get me to run it one
again. So, the idea would be to have a
stainless steel uh cylinder and put some
neutral plates.
You know what I mean? Neutral tubes.
Yeah, we've explained that on the um the
video before. Yeah, it's already
explained. So, that's what you know what
to look at when I say that. that then
will give you what you need because if
you don't do that then you have big
units like what you have here now and so
on. You're going to use a lot of
amperage. Um you're going to flatten
batteries. It's not going to do what you
want. You're going to end up in trouble
that way. I've already had those big
ones running and 10 minutes you flatten
the battery and drown the alternator.
Every bit of That's if you don't have
the neutral plates in it or if you
That's if you don't. But if you do it
come smaller units like you. But what
about in the big units? Can you put can
we put floaters in there and bring it
down to five or seven amps or something?
You in big you can. I don't care how big
you make them. You can put as long as
you got floaters in there. You bring the
amperage down. You bring the ampage
down. So the current seems to go from a
positive and a negative. And instead of
staying at that whatever it's going to
use or pull or whatever, it then seems
to break them down and bring them back
the opposite way, but produces twice the
gas. You've already seen that on video.
It shows you put a neutral one in there,
you use a lot of amperage. I mean, you
put positive and negative, just single
plates. You use a lot of
amperage and you don't seem to get off
the gas you want. So the idea will be if
you are trying to run a vehicle and use
a a positive and a negative in it just
singly, you're going to have to go
bigger units. But to do that, you're
going the wrong way because then you
need heaps of flame in the air, you need
bigger batteries, you need more current
to run it. So that isn't the way to go,
right?